[{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678881348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14350,"timeElapsed":107495},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4879,"timeElapsed":112376},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678893319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7088,"timeElapsed":119466},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678912366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":19046,"timeElapsed":138513},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678920121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7754,"timeElapsed":146268},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678932106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":11984,"timeElapsed":158253},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678938726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6619,"timeElapsed":164873},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678949724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":10997,"timeElapsed":175871},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3552,"timeElapsed":179424},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678964446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9398,"timeElapsed":190593},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678969166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4719,"timeElapsed":195313},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3589,"timeElapsed":198903},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678978077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5320,"timeElapsed":204224},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1849,"timeElapsed":206074},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678983730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3802,"timeElapsed":209877},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1640,"timeElapsed":211518},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5014,"timeElapsed":216532},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":218664},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679003427,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10908,"timeElapsed":229573},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":8649,"timeElapsed":239599},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":243599},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679021369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3916,"timeElapsed":247515},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4105,"timeElapsed":251622},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1761,"timeElapsed":253384},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4389,"timeElapsed":257774},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1459,"timeElapsed":259233},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3306,"timeElapsed":262540},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679039143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":265289},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679046916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6498,"timeElapsed":273063},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3205,"timeElapsed":276270},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2845,"timeElapsed":279116},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4510,"timeElapsed":283627},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2352,"timeElapsed":285980},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3942,"timeElapsed":289923},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2258,"timeElapsed":292181},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":19077,"timeElapsed":311260},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":313208},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13470,"timeElapsed":327789},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":329992},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4377,"timeElapsed":334370},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5030,"timeElapsed":339401},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":342101},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2684,"timeElapsed":344786},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1336,"timeElapsed":346123},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679123639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":349786},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1929,"timeElapsed":351716},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5228,"timeElapsed":358172},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":360043},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":364227},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4466,"timeElapsed":368694},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5054,"timeElapsed":373748},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2890,"timeElapsed":376640},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1414,"timeElapsed":378054},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2171,"timeElapsed":380226},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1986,"timeElapsed":382213},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10722,"timeElapsed":394484},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":397122},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":399425},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4577,"timeElapsed":404003},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":405688},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3912,"timeElapsed":409600},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679185176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1722,"timeElapsed":411323},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":413545},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":415425},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5263,"timeElapsed":422072},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1986,"timeElapsed":424059},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2630,"timeElapsed":426690},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3240,"timeElapsed":429931},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":432484},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679209169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2831,"timeElapsed":435316},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1397,"timeElapsed":436714},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2754,"timeElapsed":439469},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1810,"timeElapsed":441280},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":10313,"timeElapsed":453432},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4395,"timeElapsed":457828},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679234107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2425,"timeElapsed":460254},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679236447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2339,"timeElapsed":462594},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679238904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":465050},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246868,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7964,"timeElapsed":473015},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4122,"timeElapsed":477139},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2000,"timeElapsed":479139},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2806,"timeElapsed":481946},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679258352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":484499},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6088,"timeElapsed":491953},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3392,"timeElapsed":495346},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679271463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2263,"timeElapsed":497610},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3810,"timeElapsed":501421},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2129,"timeElapsed":503551},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2938,"timeElapsed":506490},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679281894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1550,"timeElapsed":508041},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":510233},{"subjectID":"2m4ysfuol8","prolificID":"5efd22056ec55516587f32a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b31ea9a49a640663775","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2099,"timeElapsed":512334}]